<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hate Alert</title>
    <link>/authors/mithun/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/mithun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Hate Alert</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>©2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hate speech: Detection, Mitigation and Beyond</title>
      <link>/talk/icwsm_tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/icwsm_tutorial/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;-bookmark-the-page-to-stay-updated-&#34;&gt;👉 Bookmark the page to stay updated !!!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table-of-contents&#34;&gt;Table of contents&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be added soon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;organizers-detail&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizers detail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Punyajoy Saha&lt;/strong&gt; is a PhD scholar at the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur (India). His research interests lies in the nexus of social computing and natural language processing. He is currently invested in mitigation of hate speech in social media. His works are published at major conferences like WWWW, AAAI, ECML-PKDD and ICWSM.More about him can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://punyajoy.github.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binny Mathew&lt;/strong&gt; is a PhD scholar at the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur (India). His research interest lies in computational social science and natural language processing. He is currently interested in solving issues surrounding hate speech in online social media and providing solutions to counter them. His works are published in leading conferences such as WWW, ICWSM, ECML-PKDD, and WebSci. More about him can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://binny-mathew.github.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mithun Das&lt;/strong&gt; is a PhD scholar at the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur (India). His research interests lies in computational social science and natural language processing. More about him can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://das-mithun.github.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pawan Goyal&lt;/strong&gt; is an Associate Professor at the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur (India). His research interest lies in natural language processing and text mining. More about him can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://cse.iitkgp.ac.in/~pawang/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kiran Garimella&lt;/strong&gt; is the first IDSS postdoctoral fellow to receive a Hammer Fellowship, pioneers research into the spread of rumors and misinformation on closed platforms such as WhatsApp, a popular encrypted messaging service with millions of users worldwide. Kiran aims to develop technical solutions to such problems by building tools that can collect and analyze massive social media datasets. More about him can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://users.ics.aalto.fi/kiran/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Animesh Mukherjee&lt;/strong&gt; is an Associate Professor at the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur (India). His research interest lies in natural language processing, information retrieval and AI and ethics. More about him can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://cse.iitkgp.ac.in/~animeshm/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
